Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; 1; 4367
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 2008 January 16-2016 June 30; 1.3; 1315
    - College of Arts and Sciences, 2008 January 16-2016 June 30; 1.3.1; 1315
      - UAIM: 1/28 @ 3 PM CESTM group photo / UAIM staff digital, 2003 February 7; 23.7 MB 10
      - UAIM: 1/28/03 @ 10:15 AM CESTM Ribbon Cutting Ceremony / 2nd Bldg. Digital, 2003 February 7; 231.1 MB 86
      - UAIM: 3/27/03 @ 2 PM CESTM High School students / CESTM tour digital, 2003 April 2; 16.6 MB 43
      - UAIM: 3/19/03 @ 3 PM CESTM/new bldg. Spkrs in new auditorium digital, 2003 April 2; 19.2 MB 50
      - Outreach: 3/21/03 @ 9:30 AM CESTM reps from Northeast Health and scientists in lab digital, 2003 April 4; 3.6 MB 7
      - Media and Marketing: 5/6/03 @ 1 PM HU-266 Lynne Blackburn and Sarah Failla digital, 2003 May 21; 3.9 MB 10
      - Media and Marketing: 5/6/03 @ 1 PM HU-266 Lynne Blackburn and Sarah Failla digital, 2003 May 21; 3.9 MB 10
      - Jewish Studies: 6/3/03 @ 3 PM Riverview Restaurant / Hastings-on-Hudson Annual Event digital, 2003 June 10; 24.1 MB 62
      - Jewish Studies: 6/3/03 @ 3 PM Riverview Restaurant / Hastings-on-Hudson Annual Event digital, 2003 June 10; 24.1 MB 62
      - Media and Marketing: 6/17/03 @ 2 PM Sculpture Studio Chris Cassidy w/ sculpture model digital, 2003 July 3; 29.9 MB 77
      - Media and Marketing: 6/17/03 @ 2 PM Sculpture Studio Chris Cassidy w/ sculpture model digital, 2003 July 3; 29.9 MB 77
      - Media and Marketing: 11/4/03 @ 3:30 PM ES-224 Mike Landin w/ students digital, 2003 November 20; 67.7 MB 88
      - Media and Marketing: 11/4/03 @ 3:30 PM ES-224 Mike Landin w/ students digital, 2003 November 20; 67.7 MB 88
      - Media and Marketing: 11/14/03 @ 5 PM CESTM reception digital, 2003 December 2; 161.5 MB 63
      - Chartwells: 11/20/03 @ 11:30 AM CESTM Grand Opening: NanoFab Cafe digital, 2003 December 2; 96.2 MB 39
      - Media and Marketing: 11/14/03 @ 5 PM CESTM reception digital, 2003 December 2; 161.5 MB 63
      - Chartwells: 11/20/03 @ 11:30 AM CESTM Grand Opening: NanoFab Cafe digital, 2003 December 2; 96.2 MB 39
      - E2TAC: 12/15/03 @ 1:45 PM CESTM press conference w/ Chas. Schumer digital, 2003 December 26; 210.5 MB 95
      - E2TAC: 12/15/03 @ 1:45 PM CESTM press conference w/ Chas. Schumer digital, 2003 December 26; 210.5 MB 95
      - E2TAC: 2/10/04 @ 10:15 - 11:15 / 4:00 - 4:45 CESTM NY Super Con event digital, 2004 February 25; 85.8 MB 67
      - E2TAC: 2/10/04 @ 10:15 - 11:15 / 4:00 - 4:45 CESTM NY Super Con event digital, 2004 February 25; 85.8 MB 67
      - Media & Marketing: photo session: 3/3/04 @ 9:30 AM Boor Sculpture Studio "Digital Expressions", 2004 March 3; 141.8 MB 91
      - photo session: 3/3/04 @ 9:30 AM Boor Sculpture Studio "Digital Expressions", 2004 March 3; 141.8 MB 91
      - Media & Marketing: photo session: 3/3/04 @ 9:30 AM Boor Sculpture Studio "Digital Expressions", 2004 March 4; 87.5 MB 59
        2016 December 16 Submission Information Package (SIP) created with createSIP.py version 0.1
      - Media & Marketing: photo session: 3/3/04 @ 9:30 AM Boor Sculpture Studio "Digital Expressions", 2004 March 4; 87.5 MB 59
      - Writer's Institute: photo session: 3/4/04 @ 7:30 PM Page Hall State Author/Poet Reading, 2004 March 5; 67.2 MB 46
      - Writer's Institute: photo session: 3/4/04 @ 7:30 PM Page Hall State Author/Poet Reading, 2004 March 5; 95.4 MB 63
      - Writer's Institute: photo session: 3/4/04 @ 7:30 PM Page Hall State Author/Poet Reading, 2004 March 5; 67.2 MB 46
      - Writer's Institute: photo session: 3/4/04 @ 7:30 PM Page Hall State Author/Poet Reading, 2004 March 5; 95.4 MB 63
      - Media and Marketing: 3/3/04 @ 3 PM CESTM L128 Vincent LaBella digital, 2004 March 15; 70.6 MB 48
      - Media and Marketing: 3/3/04 @ 3 PM CESTM L128 Vincent LaBella digital, 2004 March 15; 70.6 MB 48
      - Media and Marketing: 4/1/04 @ 4 PM HU-254 East Asian Studies / Tibet trip digital, 2004 April 16; 162.8 MB 47
      - Media and Marketing: 4/1/04 @ 4 PM HU-254 East Asian Studies / Tibet trip digital, 2004 April 16; 162.8 MB 47
      - Media and Marketing: 11/8/04 @ 3 PM CESTM portrait: Robert Geer digital, 2004 November 19; 49.9 MB 29
      - Media and Marketing: 11/8/04 @ 3 PM CESTM portrait: Robert Geer digital, 2004 November 19; 51.4 MB 30
      - Media and Marketing: 11/8/04 @ 3 PM CESTM portrait: Robert Geer digital, 2004 November 19; 51.4 MB 30
      - Media and Marketing: 11/22/04 @ 2 PM PAC 212 Music Students w/ Findley Cockrell digital, 2004 December 7; 212.2 MB 143
      - Media and Marketing: 12/7/04 @ 2 PM CESTM Prof. Kathleen Dunn w/ students: Jonathan Rullan and Susan Huang digital, 2004 December 17; 181.2 MB 145
      - Media and Marketing: 12/15/04 @ 3:30 PM AS111A Stuart Swiny w/ students: Elena Stylianou, Katie Alois, Isaac Samuels and David Hanssen digital, 2004 December 23; 101.0 MB 68
      - Media and Marketing: 2/8/05 @ 3 PM Provosts Office UAB Len Slade w/students digital, 2005 February 15; 42.2 MB 26
      - Media and Marketing: 5/5/05 @ 3:45 - 4:30 PM PAC Studio Theater / Recital Hall Ruby Dee digitaly, 2005 March 31; 76.0 MB 50
      - Arts & Sciences: 5/2/05 @ 9 AM AS 122 group photo, 2005 May 16; 31.3 MB 23
      - ITM: 5/3/05 @ Noon BA 233 group photo: Sanyay Goel's class, 2005 May 17; 25.3 MB 13
      - CAS: 6/21/05 @ 11 AM Arts and Sciences Walkway two students digital, 2005 July 5; 264.2 MB 183
      - Research Foundation: 10/17/05 @ 3 PM CESTM / NanoFab 200 Vince LaBella and Mengbing Huang digital, 2005 October 27; 93.8 MB 43
      - Judaic Studies: 11/13/05 @ 3 PM Standish Room Torah Scroll Reception, 2005 November 24; 25.8 MB 13
      - President: 11/10/05 @ 11:30 AM Standish Room NYS Assembly Higher Ed Team digital, 2005 November 24; 11.0 MB 6
      - Media and Marketing: 11/18/05 @ 3:30 PM CESTM L128 Vince LaBella and student digital, 2005 November 30; 155.4 MB 28
      - President: 12/7/05 @ 11 AM ED 346 Ed Adm & Plicy Studies w/ Susan Herbst digital, 2005 December 2; 53.0 MB 14
      - President: 12/8/05 @ 4 PM Pres Res Reception for Frank Thompson digital, 2005 December 2; 797.6 MB 135
      - President: 12/14/05 @ 12:30 PM History Dept / Ten Broeck 2 Faculty mtg w/ Susan Herbst, 2005 December 15; 60.2 MB 10
      - President: 12/14/05 @ 4 PM Pres Res All Faculty and Staff Holiday Open House, 2005 December 15; 325.7 MB 57
      - Media & Marketing: 11/22/06 @ 11:30 AM in CESTM L240 for photo of Jim Castracane in cleanroom., 2006 November 22; 71.2 MB 34
      - Media & Marketing: 2/2/07 @ 1:30 pm Assembly Hall, Campus Center for CETL Kick-Off, 2007 February 3; 66.2 MB 32
      - Media and Marketing: 1/30/07 @ 10 am ASRC / CESTM Prof. Wei-Chyung Wang, 2007 February 13; 24.9 MB 50
      - Media & Marketing: 9/19/07 @ 1 p.m. photo of 3 athropology students and professor recreating an ancient Mayan diet in the Arts & Sciences bldg., room 102., 2007 September 24; 33.5 MB 87
      - Jill Hanifan and students, 2009 May 14; 12.4 MB 27
      - RNA_Press Event and Dedication, 2010 June 4; 203.7 MB 241
    - Department of Atmospheric and, 2008 April 29-2015 December 21; 1.3.2; 202
    - Geography and Planning, 2016 June 29-2016 June 30; 1.3.3; 42
    - The RNA Institute, 2010 April 8-2016 April 25; 1.3.4; 480
  - College of Computing Informati, 2014 April 10-2016 March 25; 1.4; 694
    - MIS: 5/9/03 @ 12:15 PM BA-219 group photo / Mis students and faculty color print, 2003 May 12; 14.2 MB 12
    - President: 8/29/05 @ 1:30 PM Digital Workshop 2 / Science Library Announcement of College of Computing and Information digital, 2005 September 9; 66.2 MB 45
    - President: 8/31/05 @ 10:15 AM Pres Office Assemblyman John McEneny with Pres Hall digital, 2005 September 12; 29.9 MB 20
    - President: 8/31/05 @ 1 PM - 2 PM Science Library - Conference Room Albany Symphony Board Briefing digital, 2005 September 12; 19.6 MB 13
    - President: 9/7/05 @ 8:30 AM - 10:00 AM Standish Room President for a day digital, 2005 September 12; 35.1 MB 25
    - President: 9/7/05 @ 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM Location TBA Executive Committee Meeting digital, 2005 September 12; 28.9 MB 22
    - CCI: head shots of all CCI faculty on 8/24 between 2:30 - 3:30 p.m. in the Standish Room * Please set up for this in the a.m. before you take off to the S.O.B. job., 2007 August 24; 52.2 MB 109
    - CCI: photos of grad students and T.A.'s at CSI oreintation of 8/28/07 in LI-98 (computer science conference room) at 4 p.m., general shots of interaction, 2007 September 5; 10.2 MB 19
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: Move-in day photos to include general shots of students moving in, a male and female student laden down with belongings, different ethnicities, Susan Herbt helping out, parents hugging their child, etc. Also, photos of check presentation from Holiday Inn at 10:45 a.m. at State Quad on the steps or under a canopy if rain., 2007 September 5; 176.5 MB 179
    - CCI: 9/26/07 @ 4 pm atrium in LSRB to take shots of CCI staff and sudents., 2007 October 10; 142.5 MB 196
    - CCI: 10/9/07 from 1 - 4 p.m. and 10/11/07 from 9 - 12 p.m. to take group shots of CCI students through the Science library, 2007 October 12; 403.0 MB 546
    - CCI: 10/9/07 from 1 - 4 p.m. and 10/11/07 from 9 - 12 p.m. to take group shots of CCI students through the Science library, 2007 October 12; 403.0 MB 546
    - CCI: 10/9/07 from 1 - 4 p.m. and 10/11/07 from 9 - 12 p.m. to take group shots of CCI students through the Science library, 2007 October 12; 403.0 MB 546
    - CCI: 10/9/07 from 1 - 4 p.m. and 10/11/07 from 9 - 12 p.m. to take group shots of CCI students through the Science library, 2007 October 12; 403.0 MB 546
    - CCI: 10/9/07 from 1 - 4 p.m. and 10/11/07 from 9 - 12 p.m. to take group shots of CCI students through the Science library, 2007 October 12; 403.0 MB 546
    - CCI_Media Breakfast, 2009 December 1; 51.4 MB 98
    - Grand Opening_CCI Undergrad Office, 2010 February 9; 33.8 MB 44
  - College of Emergency Preparedn, 2016 January 6-2016 July 17; 1.5; 200
  - College of Nanoscale Science and Engineering, 2012 October 24-2015 January 14; 1.6; 124
    - Ctr. For Nanotechnology: 10/29/03 @ 11 AM 431 New Karner Rd. / Inverters Unlimited Partnership milestone announcement between NYSERDA and Albany Nanotech's E2TAC digital, 2003 November 11; 161.4 MB 66
    - Ctr. For Nanotechnology: 10/29/03 @ 11 AM 431 New Karner Rd. / Inverters Unlimited Partnership milestone announcement between NYSERDA and Albany Nanotech's E2TAC digital, 2003 November 11; 161.4 MB 66
    - CTR for Nano Technology: 5/6/04 @ 2:15 NanoFab South Atrium Reception for John Kelley, IBM digital, 2004 May 18; 119.1 MB 83
    - CTR for Nano Technology: 5/6/04 @ 2:15 NanoFab South Atrium Reception for John Kelley, IBM digital, 2004 May 18; 119.1 MB 83
    - UAIM: 8/2/04 @ 10:45 AM NanoFab South group dignitaries digital, 2004 August 16; 14.5 MB 12
    - Albany NanoTech: Photo session: 12/10/04 @ 9 AM CESTM Conference room #1 faculty/staff portraits digital, 2004 December 21; 1.1 GB 454
    - Albany NanoTech: 1/27/05 @ 2 PM NanoFab South Rotunda group photo digital, 2005 February 8; 16.8 MB 14
    - Creative Services: 4/22/05 @ 10 AM NanoFab South Citizen Laureate Bowl digital, 2005 May 6; 14.5 MB 17
    - President: 7/19/05 @ 10:30 AM Albany Nanotech INVENT announcement Digital, 2005 July 29; 307.1 MB 210
    - President: 7/19/05 @ 10:30 AM Albany Nanotech INVENT announcement Digital, 2005 July 29; 40.6 MB 93
    - President: 10/5/05 @ 10:30 AM location????? Nano MBA Program Announcement digital, 2005 October 14; 108.1 MB 76
    - President: 10/6/05 @ 3 PM CC Ballroom Fall Faculty Meeting digital, 2005 October 14; 75.4 MB 60
    - President: 10/ 7/05 @ 8 AM Collins Circle Albany High School Teach-Out digital, 2005 October 14; 350.1 MB 138
    - Ctr for Nano Science: 9/27/05 Nano Fab 200 Recognition Awards and Reception digital, 2005 October 26; 306.4 MB 85
    - Nano Technology: 1/3/06 @ 1:30 pm Nano Fab South Press Conference, 2006 January 17; 577.6 MB 97
    - Nanoscale Science and Engineering: 3/20/06 @ 1:30 PM NanoFab 300 South NYSTAR check presentation, 2006 March 24; 90.4 MB 49
    - Nanoscale Science and Engineering: 5/15/06 - 5/16/06 various times Albany Marriott NYS Investors Conference, 2006 May 30; 650.1 MB 177
    - Nanoscale Science and Engineering: 5/23/06 @ TBA NanoFab / CESTM Career Day; middle and high school students, 2006 June 5; 411.6 MB 166
    - Media and Marketing: 9/22/06 @ 12:15 PM NanoFab (middle) Alberto Bustani / Pres. Technological Institute of Monterrey Mexico w/ Ray Bromley and Hassaram Bakhru, 2006 October 3; 27.0 MB 12
    - Nanoscale Science and Engineering: 9/27/06 @ 3:30 PM - 5:30 PM NanoFab 300 South Auditorium 2006 CNSE Recognition Event, 2006 October 3; 187.9 MB 95
    - Media & Marketing: 10/19/06 @ 3:15 PM NanoFab 300 South press conference: Vistec announcement, 2006 October 19; 176.8 MB 95
    - President's Office: 10/19/06 @ 3:45 PM North Board room of the NanoFab complex for University Council group shot, 2006 October 19; 11.1 MB 15
    - Nano Technology: Photo session: 12/6/06 @ 10:30 AM Nano Fab North photo of beta tool with Nate Cady, 2006 December 20; 233.7 MB 128
    - Nanoscale Science and Engineering: 12/14/06 @ 11 AM Nanofab South?, 2006 December 27; 26.4 MB 74
    - College of Nanoscale Science and Engineering: 1/16/07 @ 10:45 am NanoFab 300 South Rotunda for Key Bank announcement and check presentation. Need shots of each speaker at the podium, shots of Dr. Kaloyeros with the various speakers and any other VIPs attending the event., 2007 January 17; 129.8 MB 81
    - College of Nanoscale Science: 1/24/07 @ 5- 7 pm South Rotunda of Nano for Vistec Job Fair. Shots: 5-5:15 there will be a registration in the south rotunda. 5:15-5:50 Welcoming remarks followed by speeches from NYS elected officials 6:00-8:30 Attendees will attend four "stations" which are; Presentation in South Auditorium, Interviews in North Rotunda, Tours of North Viewing Gallery, and Presentation in CESTM auditorium. We would like shots of attendees at each of these four "stations". Attendees will be broken into four groups; each group will be escorted to one of these stations. After 30 minutes they will be escorted to a different station., 2007 January 25; 181.5 MB 92
    - NanoScience: 9/21/07 @ 11 AM - 3 PM Science Library Atrium for Conference: Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh, 2007 September 22; 67.4 MB 142
    - Media and Marketing: 9/10/07 @ 1 PM Nano Fab Lab Prof. Robert Brainard and student Dimitri Vaughan, 2007 September 24; 247.8 MB 202
    - Media and Marketing: 1/7/08 @ 11 am College of Nanoscale Science and Education Roundtable discussion on Nano and higher education w/ Gov. Eliot Spitzer and panel, 2008 January 21; 72.7 MB 183
  - Division of Research, 2012 October 24-2015 January 14; 1.7; 124
    - Media and Marketing: 2/11/05 @ 3 PM Institutional Research (UAB 321) Gurinder Singh digital, 2005 February 14; 53.5 MB 32
    - Research Development: 10/5/05 @ 1:30 PM Life Sciences Auditorium New Faculty Orientation digital, 2005 October 14; 93.6 MB 71
    - President: 10/4/05 @ 1:30 PM CC Terrace Lounge Building Manager Mtg digital, 2005 October 14; 47.0 MB 33
  - Library, 2008 April 29-2014 August 22; 1.8; 74
    - Alumni Affairs: 9/27/00 @ 10 AM New Library Archives room Group of four alumni working on Veteran's Project digital image, 2000 October 9; 9.1 MB 14
    - Advancement Events: 4/5/01 @ 11:15 AM Science Library Atrium "Two Millionth Volume" Ceremony digital, 2001 February 13; 75.1 MB 92
    - Special Events: 10/7/04 @ 1 PM - 3 PM President's Reading Room / Main Library Distinguished Professor Unveiling and reception digital, 2004 October 1; 55.5 MB 42
    - Advancement Events: 9/30/05 @ 4 PM - 5:30 PM Science Library / Barnes & Noble Room Welcome Reception for Library Dean: Frank D'Andraia digital, 2005 September 22; 100.6 MB 68
    - President's Office: photo shoot: 9/12/05 @ 12:30 PM CC 375 MidTown Meeting digital, 2005 September 22; 50.4 MB 32
    - President: 2 PM - 3 PM Cobb Room Main Library (Basement) Library Faculty Meeting digital, 2005 November 16; 36.7 MB 16
    - President: 11/18/05 @ 12 Noon CC Ballroom Researching New York Conference digital, 2005 November 30; 222.3 MB 46
    - Event in M.E. Grenander Reading Room, 2009 May 12; 14.3 MB 6
  - Rockefeller College, 2014 February 4-2016 June 3; 1.9; 462
    - Professional Development Program: 10/9/01 @ 11:30 - 2:30 Downtown Campus/ Richardson 3rd Fl PDP Open House digital, 2001 October 8; 50.8 MB 42
    - Professional Development Program: 10/18/01 @ 1:30 - 4:00 PM Downtown Campus Symposium and reception digital, 2001 October 8; 131.2 MB 115
    - Professional Development Program: 10/23/01 @ 12 :00 noon Century House - Latham, NY All Staff Day - group photo (approx: 100 people) color film, 2001 October 8; 38.8 MB 29
    - Rockefeller College: 11/13/02 @ 2:30 pm Milne 103 portrait: Frank Thompson and Irene Lurie w/ students digital, 2002 November 20; 217.5 MB 83
    - Media and Marketing: 12/17/02 @ 2:30 PM Milne 317 David McCaffery and Emil Bove digital, 2002 December 25; 38.5 MB 27
    - Rockefeller College: 5/15/03 @ 3:30 PM Milne rm200 Burton Lecture digital, 2003 May 19; 22.4 MB 60
    - Rockefeller College: 5/15/03 @ 3:30 PM Milne rm200 Burton Lecture digital, 2003 May 19; 22.4 MB 60
    - Rockefeller College: 5/19/03 @ 3:30 PM pond/Uptown Campus portrait: Julian Zelizer for book cover digital, 2003 June 3; 16.4 MB 33
    - Rockefeller College: 5/19/03 @ 3:30 PM pond/Uptown Campus portrait: Julian Zelizer for book cover digital, 2003 June 3; 16.4 MB 33
    - Rockefeller College: 11/12/03 @ 5:30 PM Rockefeller College 411 State St. Alumni Awards Ceremony digital / Suzanne Kowala, 2003 November 24; 338.9 MB 158
    - Rockefeller College: 11/12/03 @ 5:30 PM Rockefeller College 411 State St. Alumni Awards Ceremony digital / Suzanne Kowala, 2003 November 24; 338.9 MB 158
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; 61.3 MB 42
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; 120.5 MB 89
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; 61.3 MB 42
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/13/04 @ 3:30 PM Draper 105 Burton Lecture and Reception: Alan Hevesi, 2004 May 14; 120.5 MB 89
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; 151.7 MB 79
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; 84.0 MB 49
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; 80.5 MB 55
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; 151.7 MB 79
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; 84.0 MB 49
    - Rockefeller College: photo session: 5/16/04 @ 12:30 PM Page Hall Lounge/Page Hall 2004 Undergraduate Ceremony: Victoria Graffeo, keynote speaker, 2004 May 17; 80.5 MB 55
    - Rockefeller College: 11/30/04 @ 5:30 PM - 8:30 PM 411 State St. / Rockefeller Institute Rocefeller College Awards Reception and Program digital, 2004 December 13; 142.4 MB 96
    - President: 2/17/05 @ 2:30 PM Milne / Rockefeller College Pres. Hall meeting with Rockefeller College Deans and Faculty digital, 2005 March 3; 30.8 MB 17
    - Media and Marketing: 3/2/05 @ 1:30 PM 1 Computer Drive Colonie, NY Albany-Colonie Chamber of Commerce meets President Hall digital, 2005 March 15; 37.7 MB 28
    - Rockefeller College: 11/28/05 @ 5:30 PM 411 State St. Rockefeller College Awards digital, 2005 November 18; 958.0 MB 153
    - Rockefeller College: 5/18/06 @ 4 - 5:30 PM Milne 200 Burton Lecture, 2006 May 22; 271.0 MB 128
    - Rockefeller College: 5/18/06 @ 4 - 5:30 PM Milne 200 Burton Lecture, 2006 May 22; 271.2 MB 128
    - Rockefeller College: 10/26/06 @ 7:30 - 9:00 PM Alumni House, Uptown Campus for Dessert Reception with the Undergraduates. Photo session: 10/27/06 @ 9:00 11:00 Professional Applications Class, George Education Center Auditorium, East Campus & 10:30-11:30, Doctoral Student Talks, Levitt Room, Downtown Campus, 2006 October 27; 499.8 MB 253
    - Rockefeller College: oreintation for new master students on 8/27/07 from 8:30 - 1 p.m., general shots of interaction, go to Joan's office first in Milne 122B., 2007 September 5; 67.5 MB 171
    - Rockefeller College: 9/20/07 @ 3:30 PM Milne various locations Cover Shot for viewbook, 2007 October 5; 525.4 MB 277
    - Rockefeller College: 9/20/07 @ 3:30 PM Milne various locations Cover Shot for viewbook, 2007 October 5; 525.4 MB 277
    - Rockefeller College: Rockefeller College Awards ceremony & reception on 11/14/07 from 5:30 - 8:00 p.m.at Rockefeller Institute of Government, 411 State St. Posed photos of award recipients and with presenters, also to include candid shots., 2007 November 2; 95.1 MB 173
    - Rockefeller College Awards, 2008 November 14; 123.2 MB 201
    - Rockefeller College Gad Recognition, 2009 May 16; 106.5 MB 219
    - Rockefeller College Commencement 2009, 2009 May 18; 97.6 MB 170
    - Rockefeller College Alumni Awards, 2009 November 20; 217.0 MB 271
    - Rockefeller College Alumni Awards, 2009 November 20; 217.0 MB 271
    - Dutch Visit Rockefeller College, 2010 March 1; 17.3 MB 36
    - RockefellerGrad_commencement2010, 2010 May 14; 162.7 MB 285
    - RockefellerUndergrad_commencement2010, 2010 May 16; 205.9 MB 289
    - Joseph Zimmerman class, 2010 September 22; 34.6 MB 102
  - School of Business, 2008 October 16-2015 September 11; 1.10; 438
    - Business: 1/18/02 @ 10 AM BA-233 presentations digital, 2002 January 29; 45.9 MB 40
    - Business: 12/5/02 @ 8:30 AM MBA presentations digital, 2002 December 17; 130.9 MB 36
    - Business: 12/12/ 02 @ 8:30 AM BA231 MBA presentations digital, 2002 December 17; 4.0 MB 11
    - Business: 12/5/02 @ 8:30 AM MBA presentations digital, 2002 December 17; 130.9 MB 36
    - Business: 12/6/02 @ 9:30 AM Pheonix Insurance, E. Greenbush / St. Peter's Hosp, Albany MIS Interns digital, 2002 December 20; 169.1 MB 81
    - Business: 5/14/03 @ 10:00/10:30 AM CC small fountain group photo digital, 2003 May 13; 14.1 MB 14
    - Business: 6/11/03 @ 1 PM BA 227 check presentation digital, 2003 June 25; 47.9 MB 22
    - Business: 6/11/03 @ 1 PM BA 227 check presentation digital, 2003 June 25; 47.9 MB 22
    - Business: 6/11/03 @ 1 PM BA 227 check presentation digital, 2003 June 25; 47.9 MB 22
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; 37.9 MB 24
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; 134.7 MB 85
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; 134.7 MB 85
    - Business: photo session: 2/25/04 @ 11 AM BA-220 recruitment photo with minority students, 2004 February 26; 37.9 MB 24
    - Business: 4/29/04 @ 11:45 AM Courtyard next to Business School group photo; Business Faculy and MBA students digital, 2004 April 14; 65.1 MB 47
    - Business: 4/29/04 @ 11:45 AM Courtyard next to Business School group photo; Business Faculy and MBA students digital, 2004 April 14; 65.1 MB 47